John Reynolds

Canada



cocokingdom27@gmail.com



+1 6044617995



linkedin.com/in/john-reynolds-b79432267

Summary

As I am a passionate and skilled Full Stack Developer with more than 8 years of experience working in web development. I'm good at front-end development, especially with React. Building state-of-the-art, easy to use, user-friendly websites and applications is truly a passion of mine. I actively seek out new technologies and stay up-to-date on industry trends and advancements. I can provide a clean code and professional approach to work. In particular, I have a strong passion for React.js! I focus on making my code scalable and always stick to the rules and language syntax. At the same time, I'm an out-of-the-box thinker and capable of finding a solution for the non-typical task.

Experience



Ubisoft

May 2017 - Nov 2022 (5 years 7 months)

- Working on redesign and new UI & frontend components development, improvements with React/ Redux, Next.js/Typescript, CSS/HTML, REST API
- · Worked mostly with Implementation UI/UX components, routing and data visualization
- Complex database-related job with either relational (MySQI) and NoSQL (MongoDB) databases
- Development and maintaining new user-facing features using Javascript technologies
- · Building reusable code and libraries for future use
- Optimizing application for maximum speed and scalability
- Collaboration with back-end developers and web designers to improve usability

П

Web Developer

WAX

Mar 2014 - May 2017 (3 years 3 months)

- I've worked on frontend development using React.js, Tailwind CSS, Node.js backend.
- I've ensured the technical feasibility of UI/UX designs for React and Angular supply chain applications.
- At that time, I've used React material ui and typescript, and to manage the global state variables, with Redux Saga/Thunk.
- And also I've integrated Restful APIs into React project using Axios libraries.

Education



The University of British Columbia

Bachelor of Computer Science, Computer Science 2009 - 2014

Skills

Tailwind CSS / Material UI / Bootstrap • Docker / Kubernetes / Helm / Ansible / AWS / GCP • JavaScript (ES6-ES8) / Typescript • GraphQL/Rest / Apollo / Firebase • React.js/Next.js, Redux, Redux-Saga, Redux-Thunk, Redux-Observable, React-Logic, Hooks • HTML5/CSS3, LESS/SASS/SCSS • SQL, MySQL, SQLite, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Redis • Vue.js / Vuex / Vuetify, Angular • Git / Yarn / NPM • Tests